Get up, get up.
Sis, this one tastes good.
I don’t want it.
Just give it a try.
I don’t want it, you try it.
I said I don’t want it.
No way.
We can’t let Qi Dongdong interrupt our date.
I’m going to pack up the tent.
Alright then.
Dongdong.
Don’t you have class today?
Nope.
I’ve already started my internship.
Then,
didn’t you say you were going to start a business?
Shouldn’t you be preparing or doing some research?
No need.
Dongdong.
How can you be so unserious?
With this kind of half-hearted attitude,
how can you possibly succeed?
Wow, bro, you’ve gotten good at sayings.
I’m just taking one day off.
It really doesn’t matter.
How can it not matter?
Every minute you slack off,
others are making leaps ahead.
But I want to be with my sister—
No.
You don’t want to.
Brother-in-law, I get it now.
Don’t worry.
I will definitely work hard.
Have fun with my sister.
Finally, no one’s interrupting us.
Why did he leave?
Well,
he had something to do and left earlier.
Qi Miao,
let me tell you—
Qi Miao.
Why are they here?
I arranged to meet Jian Dan.
And besides,
how can you go out and have fun without Jian Dan?
Qi Xiaomiao.
Jian Dan, you're here.
Your dress looks really nice.
Let's take a picture together later.
Sure, sure!
Why do you look upset?
I'm not.
It's written all over your face.
I said I'm not.
Alright.
I was just thinking about yesterday, Ai Yite...
You know, after his confession failed.
I figured I'd bring them out to lift their spirits.
Besides, we have plenty of days to spend together.
And...
It's more fun with more people.
Alright then.
My girlfriend,
As long as you're happy,
I’ll do anything.
Where did you learn to talk like a domineering CEO?
I didn’t learn this from anywhere.
This is just how I talk.
Isn't that how they portray it in TV dramas?
Watch fewer cheesy dramas from now on.
Lines like these...
I don't even write them anymore.
Remember.
I won't let you escape.
If you must run,
you can only run into my arms.
Yes, yes.
My dearest Star Envoy,
Please spare me!
If you’re wrong, just take your punishment obediently.
Is it tasty?
Is it good?
I grilled this using my secret recipe.
Give it a try.
Uh...
I’m gonna go chat with Jian Dan for a bit.
You guys carry on.
I shouldn’t have meddled in your affairs yesterday.
I've made up my mind.
Since we’re both staying on Earth,
I'm determined to win Jian Dan over.
There's a saying on Earth, isn't there?
If love can last forever,
does it matter if we're together every single day?
Every single day and night.
That's quite a good phrase,
I should jot it down.
But Haoruichi,
if you decide to stay on Earth,
there's something you must know.
Cheers!
Just drinking like this is way too boring.
Why don't we play a game?
Sure! Sounds good!
What should we play?
How about rock-paper-scissors?
The winner gets to ask any question,
and the loser...
the loser drinks.
Any question is allowed?
Of course!
And they must answer truthfully.
Wait a second.
What are you planning?
Don't worry about it.
Come on, come on.
With my lucky attribute as Blue Kexingshi,
this little game is a piece of cake.
Rock, paper, scissors!
You lost! Drink up! Drink, drink!
No way!
He... he can't drink.
How about I drink for him?
Qi Xiaomiao,
every time I tell you to drink, you avoid it.
But now, for this man...
Sigh, beauty really is a trap.
If you can't drink,
I can drink on your behalf.
Get lost!
Alright.
It's fine.
I can drink.
I'll win next round for sure.
Here we go again! Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I won!
Can I ask a question now?
Aiyet, I'm warning you.
What's going on?
If you dare to ask something weird...
Why am I losing again?
You know what will happen to you.
Actually...
I just wanted to ask you...
What is your ideal kind of love?
Don’t be fooled by how loud and carefree she usually seems.
Actually...
She has never been in a relationship since she was a kid.
You've never been in a relationship?
So what?
Is it a problem?
No wonder when I confessed to you last time...
You were so shy.
So...
What do you think of me?
That’s your second question.
I have the right not to answer.
Come on, come on.
Let's do it again.
One more time.
There's no more wine.
I'll go get some more.
How did the two of them end up kissing?
I...
I didn’t mean to.
I slipped.
Aiyet!
You’re done for!
I... I really...
I didn’t mean to!
Stand right there!
I’ll beat you! I really didn’t mean to!
Finally, no one’s disturbing us.
Qi Miao...
I haven’t finished...
My wish yet.
One, two, three...
Morning!
Why are you in my tent?
You asked me to stay last night.
When did I say that?
You did say it.
You literally said it yourself last night.
Eit!
You’re so dead today.
Howie!
Stop right there!
Are you okay?
Sorry about that!
It’s fine.
Miaomiao.
Why is Howie bleeding blue from his nose?
Oh, that’s simple.
I’ll explain it to you later.
What’s wrong?
Howie!
What’s wrong with you, Howie?
Howie! Howie!
Howie!
Qi Miao!
Now, are you finally going to behave?